<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have recently completed:
  Exploratory Data Analysis with Tidyverse Tools
  Modeling, Testing, and Classification
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bit About Me</title>
      <link>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PROJECT 1</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:
In this project, I have chosen to analyze the datasets provided by the CDC containing average BMI for each state (containing 52 provinces/states of the United States) which gave the correlating state’s name and ranked the states. In the complementary dataset I chose, I looked through the data.gov national data base for a supplemental dataset containing information on urban and rural areas in each state that they were able to gather and the average BMI and correlating average year-long temperature in Farenheit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>project 2</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Lauren Conner Lmc3757 INTRODUCTION:
In this project, I will be analyzing the dataset originated from R, presidentialElections from the pacakge pscl that is the democratic share of the presidential vote dated back from 1932-2016 taken by state. This includes a character variable, which is the State that the correlating election data took place in; the binary and simultaneously categorical variable is whether or not this state was considered one of the 11 states of the former Confederacy (“south”); the numerical variables are percent of the vote for president won by the Democratic candidate and year/integer that the election occured.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>